{
    "subject": "resource/Evans_Blue",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/Canada",
    "human_readable": "Evans Blue is from Canada.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9459848999977112,
            "question": "Are there any famous people from Canada named Evans Blue?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9340682029724121,
            "question": "Does Evans Blue live in Canada now?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9137520790100098,
            "question": "Has Evans Blue ever traveled outside of Canada?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9065560698509216,
            "question": "Is there anything interesting about Canada that relates to Evans Blue?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8895515203475952,
            "question": "Where is Evans Blue from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6659098863601685,
            "question": "What is Evans Blue known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6543627381324768,
            "question": "Is Evans Blue a person or something else?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5913485288619995,
            "question": "What nationality is Evans Blue?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4787357449531555,
            "question": "What is the meaning behind the name 'Evans Blue'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4075327217578888,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Evans Blue?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Evans Blue is from Canada.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8521_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the meaning behind the name 'Evans Blue'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8521_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What nationality is Evans Blue?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8521_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Evans Blue a person or something else?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8521_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8521_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8521_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8521_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8521_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8521_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8521_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8521_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8521_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8521_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8521_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents confirms that Evans Blue is an alternative rock band from Canada. The specific details about the band, such as its formation, debut album, and lead singers (Kevin Matisyn and Dan Chandler), further support this fact."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that Evans Blue is a Canadian rock band from Toronto, which supports the statement that the band is from Canada."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Evans Blue originated from Toronto, Canada, but their current members are located all over North America (including St. Louis and Dayton), not Canada only.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Multiple sources state Evans Blue is from Canada.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The context information states that Evans Blue was formed in Toronto, Canada and also mentions that the members are located all over North America with two in Canada.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information clearly states that Evans Blue is from Toronto, Canada.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}